Guide to the North Carolina State University, Athletics, Men's Basketball Audiovisual Materials
North Carolina State University, Athletics, Men's Basketball Audiovisual Materials
- NC State vs. UNC- Chapel Hill (3 of 5), 17 January 1979 (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. UNC- Chapel Hill (4 of 5), 17 January 1979 (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. UNC- Chapel Hill (5 of 5), 17 January 1979 (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. UNC- Chapel Hill (1-5); NC State vs. UNC- Chapel Hill (2 inch video), 17 January 1979; 1972 (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 4), 21 January 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 4), 21 January 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 4), 21 January 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 4), 21 January 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Virginia (1 of 4), 27 January 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Virginia (2 of 4), 27 January 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Virginia (3 of 4), 27 January 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Virginia (4 of 4), 27 January 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 4), 30 January 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 4), 30 January 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 4), 30 January 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Clemson (4 of 4), 30 January 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 4), 10 February 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 4), 10 February 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 4), 10 February 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 4), 10 February 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 4), 14 February 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 4), 14 February 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 4), 14 February 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 4), 14 February 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 4), 17 February 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 4), 17 February 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 4), 17 February 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. Clemson (4 of 4), 17 February 1979 (Carton 14)
- NC State vs. UNC- Chapel Hill (1 of 4), 22 February 1979 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. UNC- Chapel Hill (2 of 4), 22 February 1979 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. UNC- Chapel Hill (3 of 4), 22 February 1979 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. UNC- Chapel Hill (4 of 4), 22 February 1979 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Virginia ACC Tournament (1 of 4), 01 March 1979 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Virginia ACC Tournament (2 of 4), 01 March 1979 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Virginia ACC Tournament (3 of 4), 01 March 1979 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Virginia ACC Tournament (4 of 4), 01 March 1979 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Duke ACC Tournament (1 of 4), 02 March 1979 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Duke ACC Tournament (2 of 4), 02 March 1979 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Duke ACC Tournament (3 of 4), 02 March 1979 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Duke ACC Tournament (4 of 4), 02 March 1979 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 5), 01 December 1979 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 5), 01 December 1979 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 5), 01 December 1979 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 5), 01 December 1979 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (5 of 5), 01 December 1979 (Carton 15)
- 1979 ACC Basketball Highlights (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 4), 10 January 1980 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 4), 10 January 1980 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 4), 10 January 1980 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 4), 10 January 1980 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Virginia (1 of 3), 12 January 1980 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Virginia (2 of 3), 12 January 1980 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Virginia (3 of 3), 12 January 1980 (Carton 15)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 4), 23 January 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 4), 23 January 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 4), 23 January 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 4), 23 January 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Virginia (1 of 4), 26 January 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Virginia (2 of 4), 26 January 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Virginia (3 of 4), 26 January 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Virginia (4 of 4), 26 January 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1,2 of 5), 11 February 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 5), 11 February 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 5), 11 February 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (5 of 5), 11 February 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 4), 13 February 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 4), 13 February 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 4), 13 February 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 4), 13 Febraury 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 3), 16 February 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 3), 16 February 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 3), 16 February 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Clemson (4 of 4), 16 February 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 4), 23 February 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 4), 23 February 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 4), 23 Febraury 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 4), 23 february 1980 (Carton 16)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 4), 28 February 1980 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 4), 28 February 1980 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 4), 28 february 1980 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 4), 28 February 1980 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Davidson (1 of 4), 01 December 1980 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Davidson (2 of 4) (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Davidson (3 of 4), 01 December 1980 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Davidson (4 of 4), 01 December 1980 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 4), 06 december 1980 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 4), 06 December 1980 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 4), 06 December 1980 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 4), 06 December 1980 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 5), 20 December 1980 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 5), 20 December 1980 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 5), 20 December 1980 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 5), 20 December 1980 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Maryland (5 of 5), 20 December 1980 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 4), 20 December 1980 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 4), 20 December 1980 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 4), 20 december 1980 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 4), 20 December 1980 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. University of Virginia (1 of 4), 07 January 1981 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. University of Virginia (2 of 4), 07 January 1981 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. University of Virginia (3 of 4), 07 January 1981 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. University of Virginia (4 of 4), 07 January 1981 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (1 of 4), 10 January 1981 (Carton 17)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (2 of 4), 10 January 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (3 of 4), 10 January 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (4 of 4), 20 January 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest University (1 of 4), 17 January 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest University (2 of 4), 17 January 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest University (3 of 4), 17 January 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest University (4 of 4), 17 January 1981 (Carton 18)
- Merced vs. Sacramento, 21 January 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 4), 21 January 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 4), 21 January 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 4), 21 January 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (1 of 4), 28 January 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (2 of 4), 28 January 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (3 of 4), 28 January 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (4 of 4), 28 January 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. University of North Carolina (1 of 4), 31 January 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. University of North Carolina (2 of 4), 31 January 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. University of North Carolina (3 of 4), 31 January 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. University of North Carolina (4 of 4), 31 January 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 4), 04 February 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 4), 04 February 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 4), 04 February 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Clemson (4 of 4), 04 February 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. University of Virginia (1 of 4), 11 February 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. University of Virginia (2 of 4), 11 February 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. University of Virginia (3 of 4), 11 February 1981 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. University of Virginia (4 of 4), 11 February 1981 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. Notre Dame (1 of 4), 14 February 1981 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. Notre Dame (2 of 4), 14 February 1981 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. Notre Dame (3 of 4), 14 February 1981 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. Notre Dame (4 of 4), 14 February 1981 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 4), 19 February 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 4), 19 February 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 4), 19 february 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 4), 19 February 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 4), 24 February 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 4), 24 February 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 4), 24 February 1981 (Carton 18)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest University (2 of _), 28 February 1981 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. University of North Carolina (1 of 4), 05 March 1981 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. University of North Carolina (2 of 4), 05 March 1981 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. University of North Carolina (3 of 4), 05 March 1981 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. University of North Carolina (4 of 4), 05 March 1981 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. University of Chapel Hill (1 of 4), 13 January 1982 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. University of Chapel Hill (2 of 4), 13 January 1982 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. University of Chapel Hill (3 of 4), 13 January 1982 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. University of Chapel Hill (4 of 4), 13 January 1982 (Carton 19)
- UNC-Chapel Hill vs. University of Virginia, 2/10/1983 (Carton 19)
- UNC-Chapel Hill vs. Villanova, Louisville vs. Marquette, 13 February 1983 (Carton 19)
- UNC-Chapel Hill vs. Maryland, 2/16/1983 (Carton 19)
- UNC-Chapel Hill vs. Clemson, 17 February 1983 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (1 of 2), 19 February 1983 (Carton 19)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 2), 19 February 1983 (Carton 19)
- 1983 First Round NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 2), 11 March 1983 (Carton 20)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 2), 11 March 1983 (Carton 20)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill 1983 ACC Championship Semi-Finals (1 of 2), 12 March 1983 (Carton 20)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill 1983 ACC Championship Semi-Finals (2 of 2), 12 March 1983 (Carton 20)
- ACC Champs: NC State vs. University of Virginia 1983 (1st Half), 13 March 1983 (Carton 20)
- NC State vs. University of Virginia 1983 ACC Championship 2nd half, 13 March 1983 (Carton 20)
- Basketball Tournament NC State vs. University of Virginia (1 of 3), 26 March 1983 (Carton 20)
- Basketball Tournament NC State vs. University of Virginia (2 of 3), 26 March 1983 (Carton 20)
- Basketball Tournament NC State vs. University of Virginia (3 of 3), 26 March 1983 (Carton 20)
- NCAA National Championship Basketball Game: NC State Wolfpack vs. Houston Cougars First Half (1 of 2), 04 April 1983 (Carton 20)
- NCAA National Championship Basketball Game: NC State Wolfpack vs. Houston Cougars Second Half (2 of 2), 04 April 1983 (Carton 20)
- NCAA Opening Announcement, 04 April 1983 (Carton 20)
- NCAA Championships 1st half, 04 April 1983 (Carton 20)
- NCAA Championships 2nd half, 04 April 1983 (Carton 20)
- "The Return of the Cardiac Pack": 1983 Wolfpack Basketball Special Produced by WRAL Channel 5 (Live Celebration after NCAA Championship), 21 April 1983 (Carton 20)
- "You've Gotta be a Dreamer": 1983 Wolfpack Basketball Special Produced by WTVD Channel 11 after NCAA Championship, 21 April 1983 (Carton 21)
- "Attack of the Cardiac Pack": 1983 Wolfpack Basketball Special Produced by WRAL Channel 5 after NCAA Championship (President Reagan/Wolfpack Teleconference), 21 April 1983 (Carton 21)
- Raycom/Jefferson Productions Sport Network 1983 ACC Basketball Highlights (Carton 21)
- Raycom Sports Tape NC State Clips, 1983 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill ACC 1983; SEC Finals Georgia. vs. Mississippi 1983 (Carton 21)
- ACC Highlights, 1983 (Carton 21)
- The Ballad of Lorenzo Charles, [1983?] (Carton 21)
  Cassette tape
- "You Gotta be a Winner"; Valvano's "Now it is over", 1983 (Carton 21)
- Valvano Original, 1983 (Carton 21)
- NCAA Finals NC State vs. Houston, 1983 (Carton 21)
- WRAL "Partial" show of National Champs, 1983 (Carton 21)
- NC State vs. Louisville, 17 December 1983 (Carton 22)
- 1984 Summer Olympics (Carton 22)
- Old Dominion vs. University of Virginia, 26 January 1984 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 3), 27 October 1984 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 3), 27 October 1984 (Carton 22)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 3), 27 October 1984 (Carton 22)
- NC State at Francis, 19 December 1984 (Carton 22)
- The Jim Valvano Show #11, 5 Feb 1984 (Carton 23)
  U-matic
- Basketball, 10 January 1985 (Carton 23)
  8mm Film Reel
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (1 of 2), 16 February 1985 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 2), 16 February 1985 (Carton 23)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, ACC, 09 March 1985 (Carton 23)
- Men's Basketball Practice, 22 October 1985 (Carton 23)
- NC State - UNC-Chapel Hill Men's Basketball, 1985 (Carton 23)
- Quincy High School's "Dirty Thirty", 1985 (Carton 23)
- The Daily Dozen Training Drills, 1985 (Carton 23)
- 1987 ACC Basketball Championship NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill 2nd Half (Carton 23)
- Jim Valvano Spud Webb 1986 Slam Dunk Contest (Carton 23)
- NC State Stills, Chris Washburn, Lorenzo Charles, 1986 (Carton 23)
- NCAA Tournament NC State vs. Florida 2nd Half, 1987 (Carton 23)
- Ed Williams, Jim Valvano, 2 Feb 1987 (Carton 23)
  audio cassette tape
- State ACC Champs Last 20 Minutes, 08 March 1987 (Carton 23)
- ACC Championship First Half (1 of 2), 11 March 1987 (Carton 23)
- ACC Championship 2nd half (2 of 2), 11 March 1987 (Carton 23)
- WPTF no. 2, 1987-1988 (Carton 23)
- NC State Slides, 22 August 1988 (Carton 23)
- NC State Stills, 23 August 1988 (Carton 23)
- NC State Stills, Newspaper, 29 August 1988 (Carton 23)
- Spud Webb Interview Atlanta Kossover, 29 August 1988 (Carton 23)
- ACC Tournament NC State vs. Maryland, vs. Virginia, vs. Michigan, 1988-1990 (Carton 24)
- Stinson Feature, 1990 (Carton 24)
- Stinson Kodak-All-American Master, 1990 (Carton 24)
- NC State Fundamental Features, 1990 (Carton 24)
- NC State #1 Howard Player Intro Cal Berkley Fairfield Exhibition Game, 1990 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. University of Virginia Tape 1 of 2, 14 January 1990 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. Duke, 21 February 1990 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. University of Virginia Live (3 of 3), 25 February 1989 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. Texas Mid-West Reg-Semi, 22 March 1990 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. Athletes in Action Exhibition Game, 14 November 1990 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. Finland, 17 November 1990 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. Villanova Christmas Tourney, 29 December 1990 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. Virginia (1 of 2) Return to Raleigh Master, 27 February 1993 (Carton 24)
- NC State vs. Virginia (2 of 2) Master, 27 February 1993 (Carton 24)
- NC State at Clemson, 03 March 1993 (Carton 24)
- Untitled, 1997 (Carton 24)
- "Extreme Pride", undated (Carton 24)
- Final Minute of NBA Championship game, undated (Carton 24)
- "The Future is Here", 1997 (Carton 24)
- Thurl Bailey Footage, undated (Carton 24)
- NBA '88 Los Angeles Lakers win (Reel 209), 1988 (Carton 24)
- East Tennesee State University vs. East Carolina, undated (Carton 25)
- NC State Archives Video: Lou Pucillo, Ron Shavlik, Vic Molodet, undated (Carton 25)
- Good Shots, Cheerleaders, Mascot, Coach V. (Tapes 4-7), unknown (Carton 25)
- "The Biggest Little Man on the Court", undated (Carton 25)
- Kansas vs. Kentucky, undated (Carton 25)
- Sports-Tech Video Editor "Basketball", undated (Carton 25)
- Terry Gannon, undated (Carton 25)
- Cheerleader Mascot Coach Valvano, undated (Carton 25)
- Black, Jim Valvano as Bat Boy, Picture day, Pack vs. USSR, Jim Valvano Interview after '83 ("Now that It's Over"), Spud - Slam Dunk (Tape 3), undated (Carton 25)
- NC State Slides Valvano (Tape 1), undated (Carton 25)
- Lorenzo Charles Interview, undated (Carton 25)
- Frank Weedon, undated (Carton 25)
- UNCTV - NC State Basketball Segments, Lou Pucillo, Ron Shavlik, Vic Molodet (3 minutes each), undated (Carton 26)
- NC State First Half, undated (Carton 26)
- NC State Second Half, undated (Carton 26)
- NC State Basketball Promo (Campus Scenes), undated (Carton 26)
- Basketball Footage Construction, undated (Carton 26)
- Native Sons of the Wolfpack Thompson & Burleson, undated (Carton 26)
- Jim Valvano, undated (Carton 26)
- Dunks and Crowd, undated (Carton 26)
- Basketball, undated (Carton 26)
- Unidentified Interview, undated (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest, Norm Sloan Show, undated (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Penn State, [1974] (Carton 27)
- Locker Room (Interview), undated (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. UNC #1 Slo-mo outs, undated (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Virginia #2 Slo-mo outs, undated (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Marquette, undated (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. UCLA, [1974] (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Auburn, 27 December (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Maryland Slo-mo outs, undated (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Duke, Sloan Show Slow-mo outs, undated (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Davidson, NC State vs. Wake Forest Slo-mo Game Film, undated (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Virginia Slo-mo outs, undated (Carton 27)
- A.I.A. Slo-mo outs, undated (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Maryland Slo-mo outs #2, undated (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Maryland Slo-mo outs #1, undated (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Duke, NC State vs. Clemson, undated (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. UCLA at UCLA, undated (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 4), undated (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 4), undated (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 4), undated (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 4), undated (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech, undated (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Michigan State, undated (Carton 27)
- Red and White (1 of 3), undated (Carton 27)
- Red and White (2 of 3), undated (Carton 27)
- Red and White (3 of 3), undated (Carton 27)
- NC State vs. Duke at Duke, undated (Carton 27)
- NCSU Players only, (possible warm up practice?), undated (Carton 27)
- Airport Houston, undated (Carton 27)
- UNC - State, undated (Carton 27)
  video cassette
- Big 8 Championship/NCAA selection show, undated (Carton 27)
- The Jim Valvano Show #19, undated (Carton 27)
  Videocassette
- ACC Tournament, 1973-1974 (Carton 28)
- NC State vs. University of California, Los Angeles, 1977-1978 (Carton 28)
- NC State vs. Tennessee, 1978-1979 (Carton 28)
- NC State vs. Tennessee, 21 February 1981 (Carton 28)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 12 December 1981 (Carton 28)
- NC State vs. Maryland, 13 February 1982 (Carton 28)
- 1974 Championship Games All-American Basketball Hi-Lites (Carton 28)
- NCSU vs. Wayland, 12 January 1978 (Box 29)
- NCSU vs. Kentucky Regionals, 5 March 1980 (Box 29)
- NCSU vs. Texas, 10 January 1981 (Box 29)
- NCSU vs. ODU, 6 December 1979 (Box 29)
- NCSU vs. Wayland, 2 January 1978 (Oversizebox 30)
- NCSU vs. ODU, 6 December 1979 (Oversizebox 30)
- NCSU vs. Kentucky, Regionals, 5 March 1980 (Oversizebox 30)
- NCSU vs. Texas, 10 January 1981 (Oversizebox 30)